Hee-hee…
Yeah…
You feel it?
Uh!
Midnight calling, neon flickers in the rain
Footsteps echo, but I’m dancing through the pain
City whisper, every face just looks away
But I got fire, burning brighter every day
Mirror talking, says “You better make a move”
Pressure rising, got nothing left to prove
They keep watching, but they don’t know who I am
I’m a spark turned into lightning in their hands
Don’t you tell me I should walk away
I was born to make ‘em feel this way
Hear the rhythm in my heartbeat pound
I’m alive when I hear that sound
There’s a shadow on the floor tonight
Moving fast in the flashing lights
Can’t stop, won’t stop, feel the groove
I’m breaking chains every time I move
There’s a fire in my soul so deep
No rest, no fear, no time for sleep
Hear the world when I take control
I’m the rhythm, I’m the rock and roll
People talking, but their words don’t mean a thing
I see truth in every note I sing
Broken dreams try to pull me underground
But I rise every time they push me down
Heartbeat racing like a drum inside my chest
Every step, yeah, I’m giving it my best
Feel the magic when the music takes my hand
I’m a voice they will never understand
Don’t you tell me I should fade away
I was made for a brighter day
Hear the rhythm, let it take control
Feel the thunder inside your soul
There’s a shadow on the floor tonight
Moving fast in the flashing lights
Can’t stop, won’t stop, feel the groove
I’m breaking chains every time I move
There’s a fire in my soul so deep
No rest, no fear, no time for sleep
Hear the world when I take control
I’m the rhythm, I’m the rock and roll
Hee-hee!
You can try but you can’t hold me down
I’m the king without a crown
Feel the bassline shake the ground
Ow!
Every step is a history
Every move is a mystery
When I dance, I set you free
(Just feel it…)
Let the rhythm take your mind
Leave your worries far behind
In the music we will find…
Who we are
There’s a shadow on the floor tonight
Dancing wild in the silver light
Can’t stop, won’t stop, hear the sound
I’m lifting hearts when I come around
There’s a fire no one can control
Burning deep in every soul
When the beat and the body collide
That’s the moment we come alive
Hee-hee…
Don’t stop…
Keep on…
Ow!